Ending of "Hajime Shacho
The kettle and the idol
Now, let's move on to the third element, sleep.
Is it important? Sleep.
It is important.
I sleep a lot.
The longest time I slept at home was when I went to bed at 9:00 p.m. and woke up at 1:00 a.m.
From 9:00 p.m. to 1:00 a.m.?
Sixteen hours.
That's amazing.
Without waking up once?
I slept without waking up once.
And then I went back to sleep once more.
You slept twice?
Was that after you became a shrimp?
It was after I became a shrimp. I think it was really in the summer.
Were you really sleepy?
No, but I could sleep all the time.
Yes, ever since I was a child.
When I was little, I had a rule to go to bed at 8 o'clock.
When I was a child.
That's how I became able to sleep.
I spend my days off and vacations just lounging around on my bed.
It's an amazing life. I love sleeping.
Last time you mentioned that you play video games while you are awake.
You lead a very ideal life, don't you?
I blame my ideal life on my days off.
So you are very happy when you are sleeping?
I am happy when I am sleeping.
Do you fall asleep even if you have to move around a bit?
No, it's the noise.
The rattling. What's that? That's a no-no!
Yes, it is. Wow.
But recently, I've finally been able to sleep...in the car, for example.
Oh, in a moving car.
I couldn't sleep on the bullet train to begin with.
Oh, I see.
I've been commuting from Aichi to Tokyo for about a year, but I've never been able to sleep.
Oh, so you were commuting. Wow.
You couldn't sleep even once? I mean, commuting from Aichi to...
That's quite a long way, isn't it?
It's about an hour and a half.
Shinkansen?
Couldn't sleep?
I've been able to sleep lately.
I see.
I can't sleep.
In this job, there are times when it's hard to sleep.
Early mornings.
For me, it's...
It's unbearable.
I want to go back to sleep.
But then I'd fall asleep.
I'm going to sleep on my own.
Really? I'm going to sleep.
Do you dream a lot?
I dream a lot.
And I'm not the type of person who can control myself in my dreams.
But you can control yourself in your dreams?
I mean...
If I want to go here, I can go there. I can't do that, can I? So I can do a lot of things in my dreams.
What are you able to do? I've already finished with the sky. Already done? I've already experienced that.
What have you tried recently? I had a dream recently that I was on a roller coaster.
You were on a roller coaster.
I felt like I was falling.
Yes, I did. In my dream.
I can do almost anything.
Next time, I want to do something in my dreams.
If you want to do something in a dream, you can do it in real life.
What do you have in mind?
I don't know.
I want to eat all kinds of delicious fruit.
That's what I would really like to do in real life.
Wouldn't it be great if you could eat it in your dreams?
Well, yes.
So I'd like to try that.
Heh.
I understand. Thank you very much. The third factor was sleep. Thank you very much.
Oh, but it looks delicious even if you make it with tea. Really? Tea gummies?
Oh, but jasmine tea gummies... Oh, please experiment once.
I'll make some. Then report back.
524-san, Shirasagi-san, and Mohikanzamurai-san,
I sent it courtesy of Aoyuni-san.
Thank you very much.